Martin Morris

PERSONALITY HIGHLIGHTS

- Problem Solving
- Devoted and eager to learn
- Passionate about my work
- Team player
- Works well under high stress environemnts

CONTACT DETAILS

Phone:

0421418461

Email:

Martin.Morris95@outtlook.com

LinkdIn:

http://linkedin.com/in/martin-morris-531275176

BASIC INFORMATION

Currently a full-time student at QUT studying Bachelors of IT majoring in Computer Science with experience as an Information Technology Support Officer.

Skilled in a variety of programs in relation to User Interface Design, Databases, Creative Problem Solving and Software Development.

SKILLS & SOFTWARE

- C#
- Java
- SQL
- CSS
- HTMI
- JavaScript
- Visual Studio
- Photoshop
- Autodesk Programs
- Active Directory
- Microsoft SQL Server
- VM Technologies

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Information Technology (2018-Current)

Queensland University of Technology | Brisbane Major: Computer Science

Bachelor of Games Design (2013-2015)

Griffith University College of Art | Brisbane Major: Games Programming

WORK HISTORY

IT Support Officer (2018-Current)

ThomsonAdsett Architects | Brisbane

- Providing technical support remotely and locally to our offices (Australia & overseas)
- Software development for solving problems in the work place
- Creating web applications and pages
- Maintaining and securing company sensitive data
- Office 365 admin responsibilities.

Kitchen Hand (2010-2018)

Various Establishments | Hinterland - Gold Coast

- Cafe Metz (2017-2018)
- Treasure Island (2016-2017)
- Mount Tamborine Vineyard & Winery (2010-2016)